Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Even though.
We'll be right back.
覚めないから 覚めないから
確かなものを追い求めてさ
何処へ行くの 何処へ行くの
履き潰した靴のラッシュアート
出発で一体どこだっけな
いつかのテージとき殴った 言い訳ばかり探している
毎日にさよならつけるよ
走り出す列車に飛び乗った 小さくては見えないけど
大丈夫さ そんな気がするんだ
• litersの裏面じゃないか 最後はこの本来は
心の整形の体は仕組んだり 百恩のズベンドで
言お知ら さなは 帰りかけんでしょ
I was so worried about him, I've had trouble sleeping.
Oh, wait! No, I haven't.
I've slept just like a baby.
Um, what I meant was,
I know you've all been concerned.
So now you can rest easy.
Please, I'm not concerned about him in the least.
Nor am I.
But sir, you've been outside every night,
dousing yourself with water and saying prayers.
Please restore Asta's arms.
How did you know?
I went out to do some prayers of my own,
but I saw that you were already there.
On second thought, forget everything I just said.
I didn't see you, I promise!
Yes, precisely.
And I didn't do anything absurd either.
I don't know.
At any rate, I've called you here
to discuss something very important.
My, you're so serious now, sir.
It concerns that terrorist group.
The Midnight Sun attacked the Forest of Witches
to acquire the Queen's magic stone.
Fortunately, they failed.
So Asta and his squad obtain the stone themselves.
Asta really is one of a kind.
My point is, it's highly likely
we'll be forced to contend with them in the future.
So welcome!
To the Eye of the Midnight Sun study session!
You!
Tell us every single detail you know about the organization!
Everything that I know?
Let me see.
There was that surprise attack on the Royal Capital.
We Magic Knights were called to the scene.
Let's see how you like this spell!
Ah!
My Flame Magic!
Spiral Flame!
Ah!
No Flame Magic!
Solania!
Steel Creation Magic!
No spiral lamps!
Glass Creation Magic!
Fleur de Bear!
Sand Creation Magic!
Sand Armor Guard!
Anybody who's been wounded, please come and see me immediately!
Earth Creation Magic!
Raging Mother Goddess!
Not one step further!
No one is permitted to touch me!
Briar Creation Magic!
Corpse hunting Briar Trees!
Water Creation Magic!
Slashing Sea Serpents!
Mist Magic!
Solidly Sloan!
Receive your punishments!
Mercury Magic!
Reign of Silver!
This is what happens to those who dare to rise up against our land!
We crush them!
Flame Creation Magic!
Leo Lose it!
Burn to Ash!
Hey, look!
They're so powerful!
Is there anything they can't do?
There's just one very important thing to know about them.
The truth is...
I would rather give my life than lose!
Wind Spirit Magic!
Silk Breath!
But...
What they were really after...
Belonged to Captain Foigolion of the Crimson Lion Kings.
It's you!
I see.
And we don't know when he'll wake up?
Losing a man like Fuegolion would be quite a blow.
The consequences of my misjudgment...
No.
It's our inexperience that's to blame.
And there's something else.
We discovered that the pendant Fuegolion was wearing has disappeared.
The multi-coloured jewels embedded in that tablet...
No.
It's our inexperience that's to blame.
And there's something else.
We discovered that the pendant Fuegolion was wearing has disappeared.
The multi-coloured jewels embedded in that tablet...
I see.
And we don't know when he'll wake up?
Losing a man like Fuegolion would be quite a blow.
The consequences of my misjudgment...
No.
It's our inexperience that's to blame.
And there's something else.
We discovered that the pendant Fuegolion was wearing has disappeared.
The multi-coloured jewels embedded in that tablet...
The next time they were spotted, it was close to the small village of Neon.
Asta's group saw them while on a break.
How bizarre.
Asta must be connected to them by fate.
That day, they faced the group's leader, called Licht, and...
I'll introduce you.
These three are the strongest members of the Midnight Sun.
They are the third eye.
Antithetical to integrity, we have Raya the disloyal.
As the antithesis to hope, we have Veto the despair.
And, as the inverse of love, we have Fauna the hateful.
Now, let's get this over with.
Ha!
Kill them.
Spirit magic.
Salamander's breath.
Even Captain Yami struggled against that trio of powerful mages.
You're having way too much fun on your own here, Yami. You should let the rest of us in on it!
Aw, man. Just when I was about to have some kind of awakening, too.
I would expect somebody who was in your position to speak with greater care.
How pitiful. You couldn't handle a few measly mages without us.
But then, Captain Jack the Ripper of the Green Praying Mantises, Captain Nozel Silva of the Silver Eagles, and Captain Charlotte Roselay of the Blue Rose Knights appeared.
Briar creation magic!
Corpse hunting briar trees!
Severing magic!
Death!
I've been waiting for this.
Finally!
Mercury magic!
Silver Spear!
He's been weakened, but I'm not gonna risk letting him get away.
Ah, yes. I expected this from you. I'll end you this time.
You're going after the boss, too, aren't you? All right. Bring it!
My magic is never giving up!
Gotcha! So what'd you think about my magic-free smash attack?
No! This cannot be! Why do you have that grimoire? Why do you wield them?
The Demon Slayer Sword and the Demon Dweller Sword!
Those swords belong to the Master!
This grimoire and these swords are mine! I don't care if they're all beat up!
They're not yours. Give them back to their rightful owner.
His body isn't going to hold out much longer. We need to hurry!
Trinity! Sealing! Magic!
You pushed yourself too hard this time, Licht.
Our boss is feeling a bit under the weather, so I'm afraid we're gonna have to call it a day.
I promise when we meet again, I won't leave until you've tasted true despair.
The next time we meet, you'll draw your last breath.
Remember, wherever you go, the Eye of the Midnight Sun is watching!
Despite some difficulty, the Captains fought off Licht and the Third Eye.
Huh. If you ask me, I could've accomplished that on my own. And I wouldn't get hurt, either.
After that was over, an investigation revealed why the Midnight Sun wanted Fuegolion's pendant so desperately.
According to our Captives, they call the gems embedded in that tablet magic stones.
They believe that gathering them will allow them to be reborn into their true forms, with close ties to the Mana, thereby granting them immense power.
Apparently, that was the reason they targeted Fuegolion, because of the magic stone he wore.
Four stones remain to be gathered, and from what our Captives said, it seems they know the location of one of them.
Where's that?
The Underwater Temple. One of the strong magic regions.
Oh, yeah, I understand now. So we have to get there before the Eye of the Midnight Sun does, and make off with this magic stone thingy?
Thank you, Yami. I'm counting on you. Oh, and Asta.
Yes, sir!
I've never seen someone injure themselves, giving us a lose.
Please!
And so are the Black Bulls headed for the Underwater Temple.
Asta again? Why didn't he ask me instead?
The Wizard King must have taken a liking to Asta too, and I can see why.
Well, I can't.
As soon as the Black Bulls arrived at the Underwater Temple, trouble ensued.
They were confronted by a member of the Third Eye, the Midnight Sun's three most vicious fighters. Veto the Despair.
Well, it looks like you folks are having quite a get-together.
How about you guys let me in the mix?
We won't give up! We're gonna fight with everything we've got!
Combo Spell!
Flame Lightning Exploding Cannon!
Gohan!
Gohan, Howl! Embrace your despair!
No one ever protected anybody by giving up!
What?
What he said was no one ever protected anybody by giving up!
A sparrow song and a waltzing mouse. I wouldn't expect them to be so powerful. They have some unique spells for living in such a remote location.
That's right! This place is what shaped our magic! It's been woven into the very fabric of our lives.
Generations of our people have praised the Sea God with their singing and dancing!
We've been practicing all of our lives. Each song and each dance is an offering to the Sea God, to Him and to everyone we love!
This magic bonds the people of the Underwater Temple!
There's no way!
Done with your little speech now.
说得数学义与方法
Dreams and bonds. Don't speak such words to me,ucks!
Niko!
Kahono!
Where did all this power come from?
Release my friend at once, or you'll regret it!
Hold on, are you royalty?
I am Noelle Silva of the Black Bulls!
And I'm done standing by and watching while you hurt my friends and squadmates!
Water creation magic!
Seedragons roar!
Team Claw!
How's that?
You have my gratitude for summoning me, human!
Where'd that I come from?
Now be gone, my little mouse!
Mythical beast magic will be paid away!
You are winning!
Asta!
You saved me!
Not yet!
It's not...
It's not over!
You haven't won!
Asta! You saved me!
Not yet. It's not over. You haven't won! We haven't given up and we're not going to!
Aaaaaah!
Pegasper!
This is where you lose!
Aaaaaah!
At long last, after an all-out war...
Take that, jerk!
God help you, kiddo!
Geez, do you have any idea how incredible you were out there?
That was amazing!
Oh, damn. That shrimp's got some serious guts.
His power's back?
I'm taking you with me, all of you!
In fact, I'm going to blow this entire temple away!
All right! Now come and get us!
I miss anything?
Hey there, you dumb bells. How's it going?
Can I see?
Finron.
Vanessa.
Noelle.
Ghosh.
Can.
Who are you?
Oh, I'm now angry!
You guys, too. Magna, Luck, real good work, all of you.
Since you've done so much already, I'll handle the clean-up.
Who am I kidding? This is the best part.
I meant it, though. You all did a fine job.
You may be knuckleheads, but you guys pushed me past my limits.
Don't waste your time! You humans will taste despair!
Yes, despair!
Did you shut up about your damn despair already, you freak?
However strong your magic might be now, it doesn't matter.
Cause this spell slashes through dimensions.
Dark magic. Dark cloak. Dimension Black!
Thanks for toughening up my squad. Now goodbye, Mr. Despair.
And so, having defeated Veto and secured the magic stone from the Underwater Temple,
the Black Bulls had finally completed their mission.
Now then, concerning the Queen.
That stone is a type of magic item that enhances the power of the individual who wears it.
But only a member of the Elf Tribe is able to use it effectively.
This Midnight Sun is a curious lot.
I wonder if they might be descended from the Elf Tribe.
Listen well, Asta.
The two weapons you carry are all that remain of the pair of magic swords once wielded by the leader of the Elf Tribe.
The Elves.
The ones from the Legends? So they were actually real?
Regardless of which magic stones are held by whom, we can't say for certain what will take place.
But still, whatever the future may hold, we magic knights will always protect the Clover Kingdom and its inhabitants.
You know, Mimosa, I'm counting on you.
Right!
There's no need to worry. I'll stop any foe who dares to stand in our way.
Because I'm going to be the Wizard King.
You got that, Asta? You will never get the best of me.
Take a look at that. It's from that old broad who runs the Forest of Witches.
Hmm.
Fighting off the Eye of the Midnight Sun and the Diamond Army at the same time?
It sounds like the Black Bulls have done yet another remarkable job. Thank you, as always.
That's nice and all. But I feel like my team and I deserve a handful of stars to go with that thank you. Come on, man. Don't hold out.
Now then, we've had a great deal of news. Some good, some not so good. The good news is that we're close to locating the Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout.
Yeah? You're right. That's really good news. Now tell me they're not so good.
It would appear as though they're only just getting started. I'm afraid.
Very soon, we'll have to fight them again. Let's be ready.
Aww.
僕らの誓いはここにある 口ずさむ合言葉は I'll make it true
My song, my days この世界に響かせゆこう
駆け抜けた日々をいつか誇るまで 僕らなら諦めない
My song, my days 音符を書き加えてく
流りくなった道さの暗には 輝ける明日を映すメロディー
フィーズ
フリーズ
assistive usted's arms 大ô
御人はスタホスタホスタホスタホスタホスタホスタホスタホスタホスタホスタホ
Five hundred one, five hundred two, five hundred three.
You know, you try two.
Nope.
Don't be shy.
Hurry!
Hey, this is kind of fun.
Can I leave now?
Time to announce the achievements for all the Magic Knight squads at the Star Festival.
Should be interesting.
Black Clover, page 67.
A fun festival double date.
Ooh, a date.
I remember when I was young.
Time for a stroll down memory lane.
Ha ha.
Boom.
聞 look.